[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Washington"]}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Are you aware of the history?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, I'm aware that he was George Washington's ruthless chief of staff --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I -- Piers, we wouldn't be doing -- you and I wouldn't be doing this interview if it wasn't for both the love of our parents and the education we received and their focus on education.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Well, the fact is that we haven't focused like we need to on our educational system.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 96, "question": "How does she define the opportunity to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "At the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, first of all, there's a couple of things, and it's not -- it's hard to reduce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What was your biggest ever failure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJS", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I've had two.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Which was the finger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "My middle finger on my right hand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "JJ", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Because it was amputated, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Yes, they had died, different -- at different times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "VBN", ":", "JJR", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What did you learn about yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, from the one incidence in the hospital, never, ever take life for granted; more importantly than that, I wanted to get everything I could out of life, because you never know when it can flip on you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["City of Chicago", "City of Chicago", "Nobel Peace Prize"], "PERSON": ["Robert F. Kennedy", "Robert F. Kennedy Foundation"]}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "What is the idea behind bringing them to a school like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, first of all, what I -- we have, with Robert F. Kennedy and the City of Chicago, Robert F. Kennedy Foundation, the City of Chicago, the Nobel Peace Prize winners from around the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "What would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Well, first of all, it's like everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", ":", "EX", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "What would you -- what would you put into the must-do-better box?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Look, he'd be the first to say that there are -- there are more things to do in the sense of getting the middle class the economic security they need.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "How is he going to win the economic argument against Mitt Romney, who will be chucking the kitchen sink at him and saying, I'm the business guy that can get us out of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Well, first of all, the policies Mitt Romney advocate are the policies that got us into it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "But has he been frustrated, do you think, that he can't force the rate of change as much as he'd like to, and what does he blame that on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, you have to -- I'm not going to speak for him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "-- this election?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "No, no, Piers, you can't -- there's a set of -- there's not a thing to look at both the individuals, their character, their judgment and their policies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "You don't buy that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "What does being an American mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "It means a great -- a great country with great people with great promise.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Inglewood"]}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "What are you going to do about this and what does it say about race in America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, first of all, I was in Inglewood yesterday at a church, because we have to bring the ministers and what goes on in that church outside that church.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes, it's totally unacceptable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Sean, when you were in school, what was the big dream for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Well, in fact, I had been very interested in being a lawyer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "WRB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "What did you get from it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, first of all, looking out at the kids, I think this is a particular school here that we got to visit, because there is really that diversity where -- you know, so much is said about diversity in the United States and yet we don't make much use of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "And how damaged has that become, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Well, looking at this group of kids, I think, was very encouraging.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "I would agree with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Are you relieved that Mitt Romney is the assumed nominee for the Republicans, in the sense that he is, by common consent, the least right wing of the ones that were left in the race?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "You know, I -- I don't know that I feel there's enormous productivity in talking about Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lamont"]}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "How's it doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Right now we're looking to the ratification of Minister Lamont as prime minister.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "How weird is it to be, as you have been in the last few months, making a movie and simultaneously trying to revive a country like Haiti?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Well -- yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Haiti"]}}]